

Rouhollah Dehghani

PYTHON • **DJANGO DEVELOPER**

(+98) 918-362-0574

- ▼ r.dehghani.90@gmail.com
- r-dehghani
- in rouhollah-dehghani
- ₩ www.youtube.com/channel/UCjLR8wopblatLugb6NQ_xXg

Summary

Rouhollah has near two years of experience in programming with Python and Django. As a team player he is interested in devising a better solution for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools.

Skills_

Python, Django, Django REST framework, Git, Linux, GitHub

Docker, Rabbitmq, PostgreSQL

Work Experience __

Code Team Academy

Tehran, Iran

PYTHON & WEB DEVELOPER INTERN

January 2021 - Present

Design and Development Conditional Order and Order Book, Containerized Using Docker ☑

- Services: Matching engine, Stock information consumer service connected to the RabbitMQ, Triggers management by end-user, Email notification

Logging Activities Application Using Python and Django ☐

- Django application hosted in herokuapp with user authentications and activity logging features

Django Application for Online Learning and Teaching Marketplace ♂

- Django application with users authentication, Article management and online classes registeration

Iranian Railways Company

Tehran, Iran

SUPERVISION EXPERT OF BUILDING AND FACILITIES

September 2015 - Present

Quantity surveyor, estimator, draft person of renovation and construction projects

	4				
Ce	rt	121	ca	tο	C

Git and GitHub Essentials 🗅

Programming for Everybody (Getting Started with Python) ☐

Certificate of completion for terminal bash vim essentials □

Languages

English: Fluent in speaking and Proficient in research

Hobbies_

Watching series, Hiking, Hanging out with friends

Education

Arak University

GPA 18.08/20.0

M.S. IN STRUCTURAL ENGINEERING

Oct. 2012 - Oct. 2014

GPA 17.66/20.0Oct. 2008 - Jul. 2012

B.S. IN CIVIL ENGINEERING